#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/shantwana-dixit-0b1044a2 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Data Structures
Machine Learning
Python

### Languages

English (Professional Working)
Hindi (Professional Working)

#### Certifications

Introduction to Deep Learning (with Honors)

How to Win a Data Science Competition: Learn from Top Kagglers

#### Honors-Awards

Excellent Performer
Gold Medalist
Best Conduct
Outstanding Performer

# **Shantwana Dixit**

Software Engineer at Google

Bengaluru

## Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Python, Data Structures, Algorithms, and Machine Learning. Strong engineering professional with a Master of Technology - M.Tech. in Computer Science from Indian Institute of Technology, Delhi.

### Experience

Google
Software Engineer
December 2019 - Present (9 months)

Envestnet | Yodlee Lead Data Scientist July 2018 - November 2019 (1 year 5 months) Bangalore

Tata Consultancy Services Summer Trainee June 2015 - July 2015 (2 months)

Worked on a project based on ERP implementation for one of the customers of the company.

Locuz Enterprise Solutions Limited Summer Trainee June 2014 - July 2014 (2 months)

Attended multiple internal training sessions on storage, virtualization and cloud computing, under the guidance of the cloud orchestration tool development team.

# Education

Indian Institute of Technology, Delhi

Master's Degree, Computer Science and Engineering · (2016 - 2018)

Kamla Nehru Institute of Technology, Sultanpur
Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Information Technology · (2012 - 2016)

St. Fidelis College (1998 - 2012)